sign-in.at 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy | Learn How To Get Started

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets forth our policy in relation to personal data collected from users. This Privacy Policy is the integral part of Terms of Use. All capitalized terms used in this document shall have the same meaning given to them in the Terms of Use.

Sign-in is committed to upholding a high standard in order to protect personal data of our users and keep it safe and confidential. For this purpose we share you with this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, share and protect your personal data.

By browsing, accessing and using our Website and Services, you agree to proceed on the basis of this Privacy Policy and you agree with the conditions of processing the user’s personal data contained in this document. 

### Personal Data

When you use our Services and access our Website, we receive certain personal data from you. We may receive the following personal data:

  * information provided by the user during account registration, including, without limitation, personal details, user name, email address;
  * information connected with the user’s browsing activities, statistical information, information on visits and use of the Website and Services;
  * data automatically collected by our software, for example: IP address, cookies data, performance specifications of the user’s hardware and software, date and time of access to the Website, the URL of the page requested;
  * other information about the user stored for the use of the Website or information received from third parties.

By voluntarily providing us with the personal data, you agree to permit Sign-in to collect, share and use the personal data that takes place on the Website, any applications, by email publication of other property as a consequence of your use of the Website and Services.

### Use of Personal Data

We process your personal data in order to identify you, process registration, log in to the Website, enable you to view offering materials, facilitate our communication, contact you and process any requests and applications, improve our Services and Website, target advertisements, carry out statistical analysis based on anonymized data.

We have no control over and are not responsible for processing of the data by third party websites, which the user may access by hyperlinks on the Website.

### Cookies

Like many websites, we use “cookies”. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognize your device and to provide certain features. These data files may be cookies, pixel tags, “Flash cookies”, or other local storage provided by your browser or associated applications.

Cookies allow your browsing choices to be remembered and make you recognized when you return to the Website. We also use cookies to ensure that our Website works properly, to provide customized services, to target advertising displayed to the user, for statistical and research purposes and to improve our Services.

You may change your web browser’s settings to stop accepting cookies, to enable your browser notify when you receive new cookies, or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from a website you visit. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you may not be able to use our Website or Services entirely.

### Advertisement 

We use services of Service Providers, including Google. Such Service Providers use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to the Website. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on your visit to our Website and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings at Google page. You may also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.

We may also use services of the third party vendors and ad networks serving ads on our Website. You may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can opt out of some third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.

When using our Website and Services, you consent to the storing and accessing of cookies or other information on your device where such activity occurs in connection with our Website and Services.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics software which places cookies on a user’s device to provide us the aggregated usage of data of the Website. Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track user interactions. These cookies are used to store information, such as what time the current visit occurred, whether the user has been to the Website before, and what website referred the user to the web page. These cookies do not collect information that identifies a user. Browsers do not share first-party cookies across domains.

Analytical cookies allow us to count the number of users to our Website, and to see how users move around the Website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the quality of the delivery of our materials. No personal data is collected or retained by means of the cookies used to generate this statistical information.

As a user you can prevent Google Analytics collecting traffic log data.  To provide website users with more choice on how their data is collected Google Analytics has developed the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.  The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to indicate that information about the website visit should not be sent to Google Analytics.

If you want to opt out, download and install the add-on for your current web browser, which is available at <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> and enables a user to opt out. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is available for Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Opera.

### Remarketing

We use remarketing or similar audiences feature in Google Adwords, Facebook and other third party websites which allow us to reach people who previously visited our Website, and match the right people with the right message. Google, Facebook or other third party sites place a cookie on a browser. Google, Facebook or third party sites reads cookies and may present a Sign-in ad on a third party website. You may opt out of Google’s remarketing [https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated).

If you are concerned about third party cookies presenting ads by Google and other ad networks, you may visit a broader opt out page at the[ Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). You may opt out of Facebook remarketing by visiting <https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/> 

### Collection and use of email addresses

_Notifications and marketing campaigns_

We use MailChimp to manage our newsletter and other email lists. There’s no third-party tracking in messages we send through MailChimp besides MailChimp’s own analytics, which may aggregate how many subscribers open a message or click the links inside. MailChimp’s privacy policy is available at [http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy).

You can unsubscribe from our newsletter by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided at the end of the newsletter. You can also email us to update your email address, or to request that we delete your email.

We may also use your email addresses to build custom audience in Facebook, Twitter and other ad networks.

### Protection of the Personal Data

The protection of the personal data and your privacy is important to us. We do not disclose the personal data to any third parties except for our Service Providers engaged by us to perform some functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, data entry, database management, promotions and advertisements, products and services alerts, notifications and marketing campaigns, remarketing, membership authentication and verifications services, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links and providing user service. These Service Providers are only permitted to use the personal data in connection with their functions and not for their own purposes.

We may disclose the personal data to a third-party in order to protect, establish, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, threats to our property, or violations of the Terms of Use.

The user understands that the personal data is available and accessible by our employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide Services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We can only speak for ourselves; this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, or individuals that we do not employ or manage. 

### Security

The security of the personal data is important to us. We use certain technologies to secure sensitive information (such as credit card number). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect your personal data, both during transmission and once we receive it. We use the Secure Socket Layer protocol (SSL) which is industry-leading technology to help your security when you enter credit card information. We use cookies to help (anonymously) recognize you as a repeat user and to track Website traffic patterns.

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is completely secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### User’s Ability to Edit Personal Data

Under the applicable laws, the user may have the right to access to the user’s personal data held by us and to request certain user’s personal data to be corrected, edited and removed. 

### Data Retention

We retain your personal data for as long as it is necessary or as needed to provide you with the Services on the Website. We may retain and use your personal data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. 

### Modifications to the Privacy Policy

We may revise the Privacy Policy at any time and in our sole discretion by posting the relevant revised Privacy Policy on the Website. By continuing to use our Website and Services, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

### Contact us

If you have any questions, recommendations or want to leave a feedback in connection with this Privacy Policy please contact us at the following email address: [info@reldies.com](mailto:info@reldies.com).
